A Guide to the General Records File of the University Relations Office of Information Services, 1989-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
General Records File of the University Relations Office of Information Services 1989-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/6.911
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1991 January 16.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the General Records File of the Office of Information Services.
Contents List
- Admissions 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Affirmative Action/Equal Opportunity (folder empty) 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Afro-American Affairs 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- ARA Services 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Astronomy Department 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Athletics 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Budget, University 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- CBN University 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Center for Innovative Technology 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Continuing Education Division 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Darden School 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Drama Department 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Education, General 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Education, National 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Education School 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Engineering and Applied Science 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Governor's Office 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Mary Washington College 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- NASULGC (Greensheets) 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Orientation 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Physical Plant 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- State Council for Higher Education for Virginia 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- University Profile 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- University Report 1989-1990 (Box 1)